ibcjapan.co.jp 2018-06-10

# IBC Japan Privacy and Policy

### **Pre-Purchased Inventory**

#### IBC Japan and its subsidiaries respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

#### Address

We use your physical address to ensure that we efficiently serve you and give you information which is relevant to you.

#### E-mail Address

We use your e-mail address to send confirmation of your order and shipping information. We may also send special offers and newsletters via email. We are committed to providing a choice in how we communicate with you, so all marketing email messages include a way to unsubscribe from future communications.

#### Transaction history

Your User ID and password are unique identifiers that protect access to your personal profile information and transaction history. We restrict access to your individual purchase records, account balances and payment history to authorized personnel only.

#### Phone and fax numbers

We keep the phone numbers you provide on file to notify you in case there's a problem with your order, purchase, shipment or transaction.

#### Credit cards

Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and fraud protection; we don't retain them for any other purposes.

#### Spam

We will not, under any circumstances, share your personal information with any company outside the IBC Japan group, or third parties acting on our behalf, such as those involved in freight forwarding, shipping or customs services.

#### How We Protect the Nonpublic Personal Information We Collect About You

We do not disclose, nor do we reserve the right to disclose, any nonpublic personal information about our current or former customers to anyone, except as permitted by law. We take our responsibility to protect your nonpublic personal information very seriously.

Whenever we collect information about you, we restrict access to your nonpublic personal information to our employees and those third parties who need the information to respond to your inquiries, to provide better customer service, and to provide products, services and other information you have requested from us. We explain the importance of protecting your nonpublic personal information to our employees and take appropriate measures to enforce employee responsibilities regarding our Privacy Policy.

We also maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of the information we collect. We require any third party who receives information about you from us to agree to keep that information confidential and to use the information only as permitted by law.

We appreciate your business and the opportunity to assist you in understanding our Privacy Policy. We hope that you have found this information to be useful and we appreciate the opportunity to continue to serve you in the future. If you have any questions about our privacy policies, please feel free to contact us.

#### Cookies Policy

Last modified: April 12, 2016 

IBC Japan takes your security seriously. In the spirit of transparency, this Cookies Policy provides detailed information about how and when we use cookies.  Learn More >>
